OK so let's get started with the dialogue.
好的，让我们开始对话。
One person the guest I've written here.
一个人，我在这里写的客人。
Gee that stands for.
哎呀，代表。
Guest is calling the vault the anvil hotel.
客人称金库为铁砧旅馆。
I don't think that's a real hotel.
我不认为那是一家真正的酒店。
I've I've used this word.
我用过这个词。
It means something completely different.
这意味着完全不同的东西。
But it's a funny word I enjoy I enjoy the sound of it.
但这是一个有趣的词，我喜欢我喜欢它的声音。
So I've decided to make up a hotel called the envelop.
所以我决定制作一家叫做信封的旅馆。
If there's really a hotel called the anvil effect it's very cool.
如果真的有一个叫铁砧效应的酒店，那就太酷了。
And then this one are will be our receptionist.
然后这个人将成为我们的接待员。
Now the receptionist is the person who works at the often the front desk of the hotel.
现在的接待员是经常在酒店前台工作的人。
This person is sometimes called the front desk person so they could be called a receptionist.
此人有时被称为前台人员，因此他们可以称为接待员。
They could be called a front desk person.
他们可以称为前台人员。
Sometimes this person is called up a clerk but usually front desk person and receptionist.
有时这个人被称为文员，但通常是前台人员和接待员。
We have our receptionist.
我们有我们的接待员。
We have our guest and this is the very beginning.
我们有我们的客人，这是一个开始。
This is how the receptionist may answer the phone.
这就是接待员接电话的方式。
Hello.
你好。
Thank you for calling the vault boom vault hotel.
感谢您致电金库繁荣金库酒店。
My name is Luke.
我叫卢克。
How may I help you.
请问有什么可以帮你。
This is a very common beginning to any sort of service phone call anytime you call a company and a customer
每当您致电公司和客户时，这对于任何类型的服务电话来说都是一个非常常见的开始
service person answers.
服务人员回答。
They'll probably say how may I help you.
他们可能会说我可以怎样帮助你。
How can I help you.
我怎么帮你。
OK yeah hello I'm calling to book a room.
好的，是的，您好，我正在打电话预定房间。
OK.
好的。
Can we say reserve a room.
我们可以说预订一个房间。
Can we say make a reservation.
我们可以说预订吗？
Yeah I suppose you can.
是的，我想你可以。
You could say reserve a room.
你可以说预订房间。
Book a room make a reservation however book a room is generally the most common way to express the idea
预订房间 预订房间通常是表达想法的最常见方式
of doing it in advance.
提前做。
Now the most important information is usually not your personal information.
现在最重要的信息通常不是您的个人信息。
At the beginning that's actually not so important right from the start.
一开始，这实际上从一开始就不是那么重要。
So you don't always have to say your name at the beginning because they're probably the receptionist
所以你不必总是一开始就说你的名字，因为他们可能是接待员
is probably not writing it down but you should give them the details of the reservation the details
可能没有写下来，但你应该给他们预订的细节细节
of the booking.
的预订。
OK.
好的。
Most important is generally the dates you want to book.
最重要的通常是您要预订的日期。
So they'll probably ask which dates would you like to book.
所以他们可能会问你想预订哪些日期。
Now this person could say the guests could say yeah hello.
现在这个人可以说客人可以打招呼了。
They don't have to say yeah you could say hello or you could say hi hi I'm calling to book a room when
他们不必说是的，你可以打个招呼，或者你可以打个招呼，我打电话预定房间
we want to say our purpose in calling.
我们想说说我们打电话的目的。
I'm calling to I'm calling to is very very common.
我打电话给我打电话给是非常非常常见的。
Any type of situation where you want to get something done.
您想要完成某事的任何类型的情况。
You could say I'm calling to book a room from the.
你可以说我正在打电话预订房间。
And you could say this one and then they're not asking but generally they will ask so that you know
你可以说这个，然后他们不会问，但通常他们会问，这样你就知道了
that they're ready to hear what you're going to say the dates you're going to say they might not be
他们已经准备好听你要说什么你要说的日期他们可能不是
ready.
准备好。
So it's a good idea to just say one step at a time.
因此，一次只说一步是个好主意。
One thing you should not do in this sort of situation is say all of the details together.
在这种情况下你不应该做的一件事就是把所有的细节都说在一起。
Yes I'd like to book a room between the 18th and the 22nd and I'd like it to be on the 22nd floor and
是的，我想在 18 号和 22 号之间预订一个房间，我希望它在 22 楼，并且
I want blah blah blah and my name is blah blah blah my phone number is blah.
我想要废话废话，我的名字是废话废话，我的电话号码是废话。
Don't do that.
不要那样做。
Do you think they're writing down everything very quickly.
你认为他们很快就写下了所有的东西。
No.
不。
One step at a time.
一步一步来。
Follow their pace.
跟随他们的步伐。
Wait for them the receptionist or the person on the other end who is going to be putting your information
等待他们接待员或另一端将提供您的信息的人
in the system.
在系统中。
Wait for them to ask the question because they need to be ready.
等待他们提出问题，因为他们需要做好准备。
You know what you want.
你知道你想要什么。
OK.
好的。
Which dates.
哪个日期。
Which dates would you like to book.
您想预订哪些日期。
Now.
现在。
Sometimes they'll say how many nights how many nights.
有时他们会说多少个晚上多少个晚上。
So sometimes when we're booking a hotel instead of dates we use nights because you're staying overnight.
因此，有时当我们预订酒店而不是日期时，我们会使用晚上，因为您要过夜。
We don't say days because actually the most important thing that they need to know is the number of
我们不说天数，因为实际上他们需要知道的最重要的事情是
nights because you're checking out on the last one but you're not staying for that night.
晚上，因为您要检查最后一晚，但您不会住那晚。
So for example if you want to stay three nights the twenty third the 24th and the 25th that's the night
因此，例如，如果您想在 24 日 23 日和 25 日住三晚
of the 25th.
25 日。
OK.
好的。
So you're going to check out on the twenty sixth.
所以你要在第 26 天退房。
So you're staying.
所以你留下来。
Twenty third 24th 25th checking out on the twenty sixth.
二十三 24 25 签出 26 号。
You're leaving on the 26.
你26号出发。
You're not staying the night of the twenty sixth.
你不会在二十六号的晚上留下来。
If that makes sense you're always checking out on the following day.
如果这是有道理的，你总是在第二天退房。
That's why it's more clear to use nights when you're talking about a hotel.
这就是为什么在谈论酒店时使用夜晚更清楚的原因。
OK.
好的。
Now could we do what we learned before in our technical descriptions class where we say between the
现在我们可以做我们之前在技术描述课上学到的东西吗？
20 or between the 18th and the 22nd.
20 日或 18 日至 22 日之间。
Yeah yeah.
是啊。
You can do that.
你可以这样做。
You could say between the 18th and the 22nd.
你可以说在 18 日和 22 日之间。
OK.
好的。
So generally that's how we'll do the beginning of the call.
所以一般来说，这就是我们开始通话的方式。
They might start with the room type but we'll go to the room type next.
他们可能会从房间类型开始，但我们接下来会进入房间类型。
So it could could be a different order.
所以它可能是一个不同的顺序。
It doesn't have to be this order but generally they want to know when you're going to stay.
不一定是这个顺序，但通常他们想知道你什么时候留下来。
And sometimes they want some clarification.
有时他们需要一些澄清。
So we'll talk about that too.
所以我们也会讨论这个。